Guide to the Roy Lee Williams papers 1974-1983 IBT0027
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- United States vs. Dorfman, et al (Roy Williams Bribery Case) [2/2], 1982 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Teamsters Affiliates Pension Plan, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- The International Teamster Magazine Development, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Duke Zeller - Correspondence, Press Releases and News Clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Consolidated Financial Statements and Independent Auditors' Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- General Executive Board Meeting - April 13, 1982 [1/2] (Box 19, Folder 3)
- General Executive Board Meeting - April 13, 1982 [2/2] (Box 19, Folder 4)
- UPS Master Agreement Contract Proposals [1/3], 1982 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- UPS Master Agreement Contract Proposals [2/3], 1982 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- UPS Master Agreement Contract Proposals [3/3], 1982 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- UPS Master Agreement Contract Proposals, Articles 1-37, 1982 February 3 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Central Conference UPS Contract Proposals, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Central Conference UPS Contract Supplements, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Eastern Conference UPS Contract Proposals, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Eastern Conference UPS Contract Supplements, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Southern Conference UPS Contract Proposals, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Southern Conference UPS Contract Supplements, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Western Conference UPS Contract Proposals, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Western Conference UPS Contract Supplements, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Ohio Mine Operators Directory, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- "Litigation Involving the IBT" Reports to the General Executive Board, 1976-1983 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board Meeting - January 25, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board Meeting Minutes - October 29, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Out-of-Work Benefits Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- IBT Proposed Constitution and By-Laws, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Local Union Roster, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- United States vs. IBT Local 560, et al, Racketeering Case [1/2], 1982 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- United States vs. IBT Local 560, et al, Racketeering Case [2/2], 1982 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- United States vs. IBT Local 560, et al, Racketeering Case Materials, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Raymond Donovan vs. Frank Fitzsimmons, et al, Central States Pension Fund Case, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- National Grievance Committee, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Labor-Management Racketeering Act Hearing Transcript, 1983 March 15 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Labor-Management Racketeering Act Hearings, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- George Lehr - Executive Director, Central States Pension Fund, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Central States Pension Fund, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Teamsters Information Terminal Accounting Network (TITAN) Status Reports [1/2], 1982 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Teamsters Information Terminal Accounting Network (TITAN) Status Reports [2/2], 1982 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- 1981 Health & Welfare & Pension Report, 1981 September (Oversize 24, Folder 1)